seriable.com 2014-04-28

# Privacy Policy - Seriable

**Seriable Privacy Policy**

Seriable.com takes your privacy _**very**_ seriously and is committed to protecting your privacy on its web sites. We do not disclose personally identifiable information about our visitors, other than described below.

**Type of Information Collected**

Seriable.com  does not collect personally identifiable information from our visitors unless they give it to us voluntarily. Personal information may include referring site, username, email. The personal information volunteered by visitors is only used to fulfil your request, provide you with information and improve our site for the benefit of our visitors.

Seriable.com  may also collect personally identifiable information such as Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. This enables us to safe-guard our web sites and other users from spam activity, etc.

**Use of Personally Identifiable Information**

Seriable.com  shall never sell or transfer your personally identifiable information to unaffiliated third parties without your approval.

You may choose to sign up for Seriable.com email newsletter and can an opt-out at any time.

Our website reserves the right to perform statistical analysis of user behaviour and characteristics in order to measure the activity and interest in areas of the site to further improve our website.

Like most online web sites, Seriable.com may use “cookies” on pages of our site to better serve our repeat visitors and to provide us with feedback on how to improve certain areas of the site. “Cookies” are small text files sent by a web site to a web browser and placed on your computer. The cookies used by Fringe Bloggers contain only the information you submit. For example, the cookies may make leaving a comment on our site easier by remembering your username on your return visit, or inform you know which poll option you voted for, etc. Therefore the visitor has control over the information that is stored in the cookie. The cookies normally expire after 6 months. There is a simple procedure in most web browsers that you can set to notify you when a cookie is sent to you. Visitors can accept or delete cookies at any time via your browser settings, with the knowledge that it may prevent them from interacting with the site at an optimum level. The information collected from these cookies is only used by Seriable.com and is not transferred in any way to outside vendors.

We only use personally identifiable information insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the visitors interaction with Seriable.com .

**Third Party Cookies**

Our web site uses third party ad servers (e.g. DoubleClick) to serve the advertisements that you see on some pages of our web site. DoubleClick may use cookies to help serve their advertisements, but it will not collect personally identifiable information about our visitors. For more information on DoubleClick’s cookie policy, please click here.

Seriable.com  will not rent or sell personally identifying information to anyone. Other than its operators Seriable.com discloses personally identifying information only when required to do so – for example, if requested by the law or if Seriable.com believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the rights of Seriable.com , its network web sites, partners, or the public at large.

**Contests and Giveaways**

Seriable may run contests, competitions or giveaways for its readers, newsletter and other subscribers. In the case of a dispute, Seriable.com has the final say on  contests, competitions or giveaways.

**Amazon Affiliation**

Seriable.com participates in the Amazon affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for sites to earn small advertising fees by linking to Amazon.com, where appropriate.

**Privacy Policy Changes**

Seriable.com  may update its privacy policy from time to time at Seriable.com discretion. Seriable.com encourages visitors to regularly check this page for any changes, updates or amendments to the Seriable.com privacy policy. Your continued use of Seriable.com after any change will constitute acceptance of such change.

If you would like to speak to Seriable.com about our Privacy Policy, please contact us using info [@] Seriable.com.

Attribution for this Privacy Policy goes to the [Automatic Privacy Policy](http://automattic.com/privacy/), which is available under the[ Creative Commons Attribution-Share Alike 2.5 Generic License](http://go2.wordpress.com/?id=725X1342&site=automattic.wordpress.com&url=http%3A%2F%2Fcreativecommons.org%2Flicenses%2Fby-sa%2F2.5%2F&sref=http%3A%2F%2Fautomattic.com%2Fprivacy%2F).

See Also:
